<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on David Sedley</title>
    <link>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on David Sedley</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rara avis (infrequent flyer)</title>
      <link>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/flying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/flying/</guid>
      <description>For twelve years I had a notice posted here asking to hear from other academics who have substantially reduced their flying or are keen to do so, and from anyone with information on practical alternatives to academic travel, e.g. high-quality video-conferencing.&#xA;When I updated the page in January 2021, the situation had changed almost beyond recognition. Because of Coronavirus, academic travel had largely ceased. And we had learnt a lot about holding travel-free academic meetings through remote links.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video and audio</title>
      <link>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/audio_video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/audio_video/</guid>
      <description>Audio In Our Time (with Melvyn Bragg, BBC Radio 4): Stoicism, March 2005 Socrates, September 2007 Epicureanism, February 2013 The Forum (with Bridget Kendal, BBC World Service): Epicureanism, April 2020 Other: Socrates vs Darwin, May 2009, Lady Margaret Lecture, Christ’s College - Podcast interview on Stoicism with Peter Adamson, January 2012 T Video Ancient atheism, interview with Tim Whitmarsh, August 2013 Godlikeness, valedictory lecture, May 2014 Plato&amp;rsquo;s theory of Forms, Royal Institute of Philosophy lecture, December 2014 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work in progress</title>
      <link>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/work_in_progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://DavidSedley.github.io/other/work_in_progress/</guid>
      <description>Articles and conference/seminar papers ‘Divine anonymity’ ‘Theological dualism and the origins of Greek philosophy’ ‘A Parmenidean self-exegesis&amp;rsquo; = &amp;lsquo;Parménide, exégète de Parménide&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Plato&amp;rsquo;s Parmenides and the Fourth Man&amp;rsquo; (for a SAGP Zoom panel, 4 Nov. 2023) &amp;lsquo;The Argument from Relatives&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Plato and Stoic ontology&amp;rsquo;(for a SAGP Zoom panel, Nov. 2024) Books A volume of 12 selected papers on ancient philosophy, in French translation, in the series ᾽Tradition de la pensée classique&amp;rsquo;, ed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
